<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN"    "http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd"><html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><head>    <meta name="generator"          content="HTML Tidy for Windows (vers 25 March 2009), see www.w3.org" />    <meta content="text/html; charset=us-ascii"          http-equiv="content-type" />    <title>Electric Commander Plugin for REST</title>    <link rel="stylesheet"          href="../../plugins/@PLUGIN_KEY@/pluginhelp.css"          type="text/css"          media="screen" /></head><body>    <div class="help">        <h1 id="arynga">Arynga</h1>        <p>Plugin Version 1.0.0.021</p>        <hr/>        <p><strong>Arynga’s AppDynamics</strong> is an intelligent platform for remote software, firmware, and data management for connected vehicles.</p>        <h3 id="arynga-links">Arynga links</h3>        <p>More information can be found at <a href="http://www.arynga.com/">Arynga website</a>.</p>        <h3 id="electric-flow-integration-to-appdynamics">Electric Flow Integration to AppDynamics</h3>        <p>EC-AppDynamics calls the RESTful AppDynamics web service using HTTP Requests and passes the user-provided parameters. Only essential parameters are required to work with AppDynamics service.</p>        <p>The ElectricFlow plugin for Arynga’s AppDynamics supports:</p>        <ul>        <li>various REST-messages to work with AppDynamics service</li>        </ul>        <h3 id="integrated-version">Integrated Version</h3>        <p>This plugin was developed and tested against: </p>        <ul>        <li>ElectricFlow server v. 5+</li>        </ul>        <h3 id="plugin-procedures">Plugin Procedures</h3>        <p><strong>Activate group</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to activate particular group. Please note that in the system can be only one active group with particular release package UUID.</p>        <p><strong>Activate new version of Update File</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to finalize adding new version of UF.</p>        <p><strong>Add new group</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to define new group that is used to collect vehicles into one logical group. By <br/>        default newly created group is inactive - user has to explicitly activate it. Release packages shall be <br/>        created before this request is issued.</p>        <p><strong>Add new vehicle</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to define new vehicle in the AppDynamics system.</p>        <p><strong>Add new version to Release Package</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to create new version of Release Package. Update Files versions (at elast one version of one Update File) shoud be added to new version of Release Package. If Update Files versions was added correctly, Release Package version could be activated. Update cannot ommit versions with freeze flag set to “yes”, even if there is newer version of RP.</p>        <p><strong>Add new version to Update File</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to create new version of Release Package. Update Files versions (at elast one version of one Update File) shoud be added to new version of Release Package. If Update Files versions was added correctly, Release Package version could be activated. Update cannot ommit versions with freeze flag set to “yes”, even if there is newer version of RP.</p>        <p><strong>Assign UF to new version of Release Package</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to assign particular UF to version.</p>        <p><strong>Check if RP is in a group</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to check if Release Package is in a group</p>        <p><strong>Create a manufacturer</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to create new manufacturer. Manufacturer name shall be unique.</p>        <p><strong>Create new Release Package</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to create new Release Package container.</p>        <p><strong>Create new update file</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to define new update file object. When it is created, user can add versions of such UF.</p>        <p><strong>Finalize adding new version to Release Package</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to finalize adding new version to RP. After this request new version is added to <br/>        RP.</p>        <p><strong>Ping</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to verify if server is running correctly.</p>        <p><strong>Query group info</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to query group info</p>        <p><strong>Query update file information</strong></p>        <p>This message is used to update file information</p>        <p><strong>Send image of the Update File via SCP</strong></p>        <p>This is to copy the update file to target host</p>        <p><strong>Send single file via SFTP</strong></p>        <p>This is to copy the update file to target host</p>        <h3 id="examples-and-use-cases">Examples and Use Cases</h3>        <p><em>Ping</em> <br/>        This message is used to verify if server is running correctly. <br/>        Request <br/>        <code>{ <br/>            "type": "Ping", <br/>            "data": null <br/>        }</code> <br/>        Response <br/>        <code>{ <br/>            "type": "Pong", <br/>            "data": null <br/>        }</code></p>        <p>Usage example <br/>        <code>curl -i -H "Content-Type: application/json" -H "Accept: application/json" -X POST -d <br/>        '{"protocol":"1.7", "id": null, "session": "8GURNpDkLFFuF3nzLPZvTbm30lG", "type":"Ping", <br/>        "data": null, "seq": 1}' http://148.251.87.173:18601</code></p>        <p>To check if AppDynamics server up and running correctly you could run ‘Ping’ procedure</p>        <p>For detailed explanation please refer to AppDynamics API documentation.</p>        <h3 id="release-notes">Release Notes</h3>        <p><strong>EC-AppDynamics-1.0.0</strong></p>        <ul>        <li>Enables communication with AppDynamics servers</li>        <li>Procedures: See 'Plugin Procedures' section above</li>        <li>Added procedures to StepPicker</li>        <li>Added configuration management</li>        </ul>    </div></body></html>